statclash.com 2015-06-15

# StatClash | Privacy Policy

##  Privacy Policy 

**Privacy Policy  
** StatClash understands the importance of privacy issues and protecting the sensitive information of its customers. This Privacy Policy statement outlines the types of information StatClash collects via our website, how StatClash use information, and whom we may share it with. This Privacy Policy also defines the measures we take to protect the security of this information and other sensitive data. Please read over this information carefully and recognize that any use of statclash.com and information provided to the website is bound by this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions. 

**Information StatClash Collects  
** StatClash will request and collect personal information for various reasons. This information includes: a) name; b) mailing address; c) billing address; d) email address; e) credit card information; f) Pay Pal account information; g) telephone number h) Social Security Number. The collection of this information coincides with the usage and delivery of different StatClash products, services, and transactions. 

Upon visiting the website, StatClash may send cookies to its users. A cookie is a text file that StatClash can send to your browser software in order to identify your personal web browser and allow us to adapt website information presented to you based on your personal browsing preferences. When the user provides an e-mail address in connection with their activities while using StatClash, we assign an identification number to that e-mail address and deploy a cookie to the applicable user's personal computer or device. StatClash can use cookies to personalize certain web pages and to help improve your navigation across the website on return visits. StatClash may also use cookies to track your visit to our web sites in order to collect aggregate data. StatClash uses both persistent cookies (cookies that remain after exiting your browser) and session cookies (cookies that terminate after exiting your browser). Users are permitted to disable cookies via their web browser settings, however this may cause problems with site functionality and affect your ability to use certain aspects of the website. 

StatClash tracks certain basic information of all visitors to the website. Our servers automatically log and store this information. This information includes: a) IP address; b) web browser; c) browser language; d) webpage requests; e) refereed pages url; f) type of platform; g)domain name; h) number of clicks; i) landing pages; j) web pages viewed; k)order of webpages viewed; l) time spend accessing certain pages; m) dates and times of requests; n)relevant cookie information. 

StatClash collects certain aggregate and non-personal information when users visit our website. This information is non-distinguishable and unrelated to an individual, identifiable visitor. This information tracks specific data like the number of total website visits and traffic of individual web pages on the site. This information is used to track aggregate traffic patterns and identity ways to improve the functionality and quality of the website. 

**Using User Information  
** StatClash collects user information in order to operate the website safely and securely while maintaining functionality and delivering an excellent product experience to the user. Much of the information we collect is used to facilitate the delivery of StatClash products, services, and content to users. We use this information in order to properly monitor, process, and respond to individual inquiries. Collecting and maintaining this information also allows us to better monitor user activity to safeguard against Terms and Conditions violations, ensuring a safe user environment. 

StatClash retains this information to contact you regarding payments, billing, tax related issues, identify confirmation, and other inquiries set forth in our Terms and Conditions. We also use this information in order to alert you about issues regarding the website and major changes, along with customer support related matters. StatClash may also contact you via email to notify you about your results as well as different marketing or promotions, including information about products and services of 3rd party StatClash partners. Some 3rd party partners have exclusive authorized access to information for the sole purpose of processing specific information or performing specific tasks. 

StatClash collects certain information when users visit our website in order to help us continually improve website functionality and user experience. Collecting, tracking, and storing this information allow us to continuously analyze the data and find areas to develop and improve. It also provides us with increased knowledge and data on user preferences and trends that will allow us to deliver superior products, services, and content to StatClash users. We also use aggregate and non-personal information for research or business related purposes. In these cases, your information is made completely anonymous and all identifiable information is removed. 

StatClash uses cookies to aid in the functionality of many aspects of the website and to improve the user experience. Cookies let us track different forms of data and allow the delivery of personalized data. Cookies store data and prevent the need to continuously reenter information. They also provide us the ability to track the efficiency of different advertising and marketing tools. They give us the capacity to personalize the delivery of StatClash products, services, and content based upon individual user preferences. Cookies facilitate aggregate data and non-personal information. They are a mechanism that specifically helps us store, monitor, and calculate progress in both contests and different promotional campaigns. 

**Disclosing Information  
** When applicable by law, StatClash may provide your information to authorized 3rd party partners for marketing and commercial related purposes to inform you about products or services that we feel our users may be interested in. If you prefer us not to disclose your information to our business partners, you may notify us or use one of the opt-out features. In jurisdictions where sharing personal information is prohibited without your consent, no information will be shared without your prior consent. StatClash, at its sole discretion, reserves the right to disclose personal information to appropriate parties in any matters outlined in our Terms and Conditions and all legal matters. 

**Legal Issues  
** In certain situations, it may be necessary for StatClash to disclose your personal information to government officials and/or other legal authorities as required by applicable law. StatClash will never release or disclose personally identifiable information to any law enforcement agencies or governmental agencies except in response to the following: a) the issue of a subpoena, warrant or other process by a court of competent jurisdiction; b) a legal process having the same consequence as a court-issued request for information, in that StatClash, Inc. would be in breach of law were it to refuse to provide such information, and it or its officers, executive or employees would be subject to liability for failing to honor such legal process, provided there is a legal basis to do so; c) where such disclosure is necessary for us to enforce its legal rights pursuant to the laws of the jurisdiction from which such information was gathered, and there is a legal basis to do so. 

**User Options  
** Users reserve the right to decline providing StatClash with some personal identifiable information. However, this may result in the failure to be able to access some or all parts of certain StatClash products, services, and content. Please contact [support@statclash.com](mailto:support@statclash.com) for more information. 

**California Disclaimer  
** Residents of the state of California that have provided StatClash information have the option to request specific information regarding personal information in which we have disclosed for 3rd party marketing purposes. Please contact [support@statclash.com](mailto:support@statclash.com) for more information. 

**Security of Personal Information  
** StatClash protects your information utilizing modern security technologies, technical support resources, and experienced administrative processes. These method help prevent any unauthorized access, disclosure, or misuse. StatClash takes extreme measures to offer a safe user experience however we cannot ensure the safety of all information, therefore use StatClash at your own risk. 

**3 rd Party StatClash Partners and Advertising   
** StatClash is not responsible for the privacy practices of our business partners. We encourage you to read their Privacy Policies before proceeding to use its products or services. StatClash provides webpage links on many areas of our websites and these companies do collect your information pursuant to their own policies and purposes. These companies may also use cookies within webpage links in order to recognize your computer and collect information on your preferences in order to deliver personalized advertisement or content. StatClash does not have access to this specific information therefore users are cautioned to review all policies of the third party webpage links they access. 

**Marketing, Advertising, and Publicity  
** Please review the Terms and Conditions for information regarding StatClash's use of personal information for marketing, advertising, and publicity related matters. By entering a contest, users agree to allow StatClash and certain 3rd party partners to use some personal information, including name, bio, likeness, and voice for marketing, advertising, and publicity related purposes in any form of media manner, domestic or worldwide, without notice, approval, or payment. 

**Privacy Updates  
** StatClash reserves the right to update its Privacy Policy at any time. Users are advised to periodically review the policy. Any usage of StatClash after a policy update will be deemed as consent and acceptance of any revised policy terms. 

**Contact StatClash  
** For information or questions related to our privacy policy, you can contact [support@statclash.com](mailto:support@statclash.com) or write to : 

StatClash, Inc.  
102 North Avenue  
Mt. Clemens, Mi 48043
